# SHARANITHA SAMPATH

2209 Stoughton Drive, Aurora, IL 60502 🏦

(630) 506-1466 📞

sharanitha@gmail.com



### **SUMMARY**

I am a student with a proven ability to learn and deliver the set objectives. I am self-driven, a quick learner with strong communication and time management skills. Capable of working independently or as a team member with 3+ years of experience in diverse areas.



## **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science | Aurora University**

AUGUST 2018 – EXPECTED GRADUATION IN MAY 2021 GPA: 4.0



#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Nokia R&D Intern | Nokia – Naperville, IL

JUNE 2020 - PRESENT

- Cleaned up over 3,000 lines of legacy code in C language
- Updated robot tests to improve efficiency
- Worked with Kubernetes and Docker to help create new a stress testing container to be used by other employees

# Admin Assistant/IT Support | Promed Billing Associates - Aurora, IL

SEPT 2015 – MAY 2020

- Provide customer services and help with billing inquiries
- Interact with Doctors and all levels of medical staff while maintaining high confidentiality
- Maintain computer systems, printers, and scanners
- Installing and configuring hardware and software

# Research Assistant | University of Illinois - Chicago, IL

AUG 2013 - SEP 2015

- Maintained student databases and created spreadsheets
- Compiled research data and published papers and research content about various plant life on the university website



#### **SKILLS**

- **Software Tools:** MS Office, Kareo Billing, PuTTY, Google Docs
- **Programming:** Java, HTML, JavaScript, CSS, C#, Python, Visual Basic, GitHub, Docker, Kubernetes
- Database: SQL Server